Fabrizio Lopez

Software Engineer - lopezfabrizio@ymail.com

I am passionate about creating new things, and I will be providing a product that gives people joy when they use it. I am motivated by feedback that I receive from my project, whether it be good or bad. I believe my experience with technologies, such as Adobe or Microsoft Office products, will allow me to be flexible in the workplace.

LinkedIn:

https://www.linke din.com/in/fabrizio -lopez-91ba50195/

GitHub:

https://github.com/fabo22

Cell #: (972) 567-8148

EXPERIENCE

General Assembly, Dallas, TX — Software Engineering Immersive

JAN 2020 - APRIL 2020

- Created a slot machine application made entirely in Javascript
- Created a social media web application named ConvOh made in Javascript using Node and Express
- Created a board game meet-up web application made in Python using Django.
 Worked in a group of other developers
- Created a social media web application using the ReactJS framework to help gamers find people to play with during the COVID-19 outbreak

Office Max, Rockwall, TX — Print Specialist & Graphic Design

JULY 2018 - AUGUST 2019

- Printed, designed, and managed multiple projects for various clients at a time
- Managed jobs that had strict deadlines that had to be met, and each job needed to be completed with speed and precision.

SKILLS

Javascript

Python

Node

Express

mongoDB

PostgreSQL

React

Django

Computer Literate

Customer Service

Organized

EDUCATION

University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX — Bachelors in Computer Science

AUGUST 2017 - Present

Richland College, Dallas, TX — Associates of Science in Biology

AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2017

LANGUAGES

English

Spanish

Community Service

Helping Hands for Relief and Development — *Organizer*

- Organized and managed various articles of clothing to be sent out to third world countries in need
- Completed over 60 hours of service